thelaw.com 2013-06-10

# TheLaw.comPrivacy Policy | TheLaw.com

## Privacy Policy v. 1.4

We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as “Data” below) that may be collected by us on The Law Network’s network of web sites (including, but not limited to, TheLaw.com, TheLawReview.com, TheLawJournal.com and TheLawNetwork.com.) This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. You may also wish to review our [Terms of Use](http://www.thelaw.com/terms-of-use/ "The Law Network Terms of Use").

### 1\. Collection of Data

Our registration process requires only a valid e-mail address and creation of a unique user ID and password. Providing us with other information is at your option, including information that you may enter in any chat room or messaging forums that we may make available. Note that your user name and e-mail address may contain your real name. Like most other web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie information. Information about how we serve advertising is set forth below.

**a. Case Reviews:**  Filling out a case review on our site means that you are subject to the [case review terms of service](http://www.thelaw.com/casereview/termsofservice.php "Case Review Terms of Service"). These case reviews are either passed along to us internally where we share your information with attorneys within our network. We also work with third parties, such as[ IM Solutions](http://www.newclient.us/ "IM Solutions"), who collect your data in their widgets and share your information with their network of attorneys for the purpose of finding you an attorney who can review your case. You can read more about their affiliate program on their site.

### 2\. Use of Data

We may use Data to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Data is generally not be provided to third parties (if you have received spam advertising then it is highly unlikely that the source is our web site) unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party; (iv) pursuant to the legal process or law enforcement; (v) within our discretion we find that an item or service may be of benefit; (vi) we find that your use of this site violates our this Policy, Terms of Service, or other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights or property; (vii) this site is purchased by a third party whereby the purchaser will then be substituted for us; or (viii) the Data or information provided is not specifically personally identifiable or may be part of general statistical information (e.g. 20% of our users live in the southwest area of the USA). In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.

### 3\. Cookies

Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements that appears on this web site may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisement. However, the companies serving the advertising do not have access to our cookies. These companies may use non-personally identifiable numbers to obtain information about your visits to our site and you can click here to find out more information about this practice and to know your options about not having this information used.

Our site may use the following affiliate programs and advertising based services: [Amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/ "Amazon"), [Google](http://www.google.com/ "Google"), [Commission Junction](http://www.cj.com/ "Commission Junction") , [DoubleClick ](https://www.google.com/intl/en_US/dfp/info/welcome.html "DoubleClick"), and [FindLegalForms ](http://www.findlegalforms.com/ "Find Legal Forms")to serve or track advertising that appears on our site. You can find out more information about these affiliate programs at these sites.

### 4\. Children

We do not allow persons who are ages thirteen or younger to become members of this site. For more information, please contact us or e-mail our administrator.

### 5\. Managing Your Data, E-Mail Notifications and Subscriptions

We provide you with the ability to manage the information in your user account that you provided to us in registration, including subscriptions to any newsletter you have selected or opted to receive, by using the “[user control panel](http://www.thelaw.com/login/member.php "User Control Panel").” Request for further editing or deletion of your user account can be accomplished by sending email via our [Support Center](http://www.thelaw.com/support/). Content or other data that you may have provided to us, such as those that which may appear in our forums, may continue to remain on our site even though your user account may be deleted. Please see our [Terms of Use](http://www.thelaw.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms of Use") for more details. Below is a complete list of URLs where you can modify your settings, preferences and subscriptions:

  * [Profile Settings](http://www.thelaw.com/login/profile.php "Profile Settings") – Email, User Name, Password
  * [Forum Notifications Settings](http://www.thelaw.com/forums/profile.php?do=editoptions "Forum Profile Settings") – Message Notifications and Thread Subscriptions, Signature
  * [Forum Profile Settings](http://www.thelaw.com/forums/profile.php?do=editprofile "Forum Profile Settings") – Manage email, messenger, contact settings
  * [Lawyers Directory Settings](http://lawyers.thelaw.com/members/user_account.php "Lawyer Account Settings") – If you have a lawyer ad/profile, manage account settings and notifications
  * [Support and Billing Settings](http://www.thelaw.com/support/clientarea.php "Support and Billing Settings") – Manage notifications and information for billing and support

### 6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. Please make sure that you periodically check the terms and conditions of this web site and our policies. We attempt to make clear disclosures to you when such material changes are made.

### 7\. Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free to contact us as provided on this web site and our Support Center.
